Zack, Arnold M. Additional Arbitration Files 5551
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1973-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold M.
5551
17 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Arbitration awards, papers.
Files of the arbitrator Arnold M. Zack for the years 1973-1975.
5664254
Box 16
Box 17
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 13, 2015
Arbitration, Industrial; Zack, Arnold
5664254
- A & P Tea Co. and Local 32, Bakers & Confectionery Workers, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Air Line Pilots Association International, vs. Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1975 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Alco-Gravure & Balt Newspaper Web Pressmen Local 31, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Allied Aviation (BRAC) Fred Williams Discharge, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Allied Aviation Service Co. & BRAC, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- ALPA vs. Northwest Airlines, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- ALPA vs. Northwest Airlines 1 of 3, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- ALPA vs. Northwest Airlines 2 of 3, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
- ALPA vs. Northwest Airlines 3 of 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- ALPA vs. Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- American Bilrite Rubber, Co., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Andover School Committee and Andover Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Arrow Automotive and UAW Local 1596, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Association Grocers of N.E. and Teamsters Local 663, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Associated Grocers & Teamsters, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Associated Grocers & Teamsters 633, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- B&M and Bakery Workers #166 AAA/BOS, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- B.I.F. /General. Signal and USWA, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Balmont School Community & Teachers Association Mediation, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Baltimore County & TABCO Oceanographic Credits, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Baltimore County Bd. Of Ed. And TABCO Jan. 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Baltimore County Board & TABCO Caroline Gerberich, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Baltimore County Board & TABCO Frank Charleton Gr., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Baltimore County Board of Educ., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Baltimore County Schools & TABCO, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Bangor & Aroostook R.R. Co. and UTU #1191, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Bay State Gas Co, & Local 111 1 of 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Bay State Gas Co, & Local 112 2 of 2, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Bell Telephone of Pennsylvania and Federation of Telephone Workers, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Bellows Free Academy Fairfax Teachers Association, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Belmont School Committee and Belmont Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Bethlehem Central School District and Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Bird & Son, Inc. & Teamsters #735 AAA/BOS, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- BOAC, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Borden Chemical Co., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Bridgeport Auto Transit Co. and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Brookhaven National. Laboratory and IBEW, Local 2230, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Burlington (Mass.) School Comm. & Teachers Association, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Canon City School District (AAA/Dallas), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Canon City Schools AAA/Dallas, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Caribou Teachers & Board of Ed. AAA/BOS, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Champlain Valley High School, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Charles Gilman Co. and Teamsters, Local 25, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Chelmsford Teachers Association & School Comm., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Chemical Leaman Tank Lines & Tank Truck Drivers, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Chester, Vt. Jan 31, 1975 - 3:00pm (Box 10, Folder 18)
- City of Boston & Boston Police Patrolmen's Association, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- City of Bristol, Conn. and AFSCME, Local 1338, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- City of Cranston, R.I., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Cleland Simpson Co. and Local 229, IBT, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Columbus Coated Fabrics and Local 486 1 of 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Columbus Coated Fabrics and Local 487 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Concord, N.H. Natural Gas, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Concord-Carlisle Reg. High School 1 of 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Concord-Carlisle Reg. High School 2 of 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Conn. Natural Gas Corp. and USW, Local 12924, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Conn. Yankee Atomic Power Co., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Continental Airlines & ALPA 1 of 2, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Continental Airlines & ALPA 2 of 2, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Courier Citizen & Lowell Printing Local 109, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Danvers School Committee, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Davol URWLPWA Reopened Cases, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Denver, Colo. School District #1 and Denver Association of Spec. Services Pers., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Dept. of Defense & AFGE Local 188 FMCS, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Douglas County, Colorado Ed. Association, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Dover-Sherborn Regional School District, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Dracut School Comm. and Dracut Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Draper Labs (AAABOS), 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Dupont & Dupont Union AAA/Phil #1430, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- East Greenwich School Community & E.G. Teachers Association AAA/BOS, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- East Haven Board of Ed. & Teachers AAA/Hart #1239, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Electronics Corp. pf Am. and IUE, Local 272, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Enterprise Publishing Co. and News. Guild of Brockton, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Eyelet Specialty Co. and USW, Local 7769 1 of 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Eyelet Specialty Co. and USW, Local 7770 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Fairfax, Va. Public Schools & Ed. Association: AAA/DC, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Fairhaven School Comm. and Teachers' Association, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Falmouth School Comm. & Falmouth Teachers Association AAA/BOS, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Falmouth School Comm. and Falmouth Educators' Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Falmouth School Committee & Ed. Association AAA/BOS, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- First National & Meat Cutters, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- First National. Stores and Food Store & Allied Workers., Local 592, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- First National. Stores and Local 592, Food Store Workers, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- First National. Stores, Inc. and Local 592, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Food Fair Stores and Local 169 Warehouse. Ees., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Forster Mfg. Co AAA(BOS), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Framingham & Mass Laborers Council Local 1156, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Fremont R-1 School District & Canon City Ed. Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- General Tire, Akron, Ohio and Local No. 9, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Giant Markets & Giant Markets Employees, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Gorton & Seafood Workers #15 Gloucester, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Grand Junction: Mesa Valley School, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Graphics Arts International Un. And Local 176-B, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Gunnison, Colorado Schools AAA/DAL, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Harris Structural Steel Co. and United Steelworkers. District 9, Local 3682, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Hartford Bd. Of Ed. and Local 1018, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Hartford Bd. Of Education & Ed. Admin. Association, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Harwood Union HS, Vermont, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Hilldale Convalescent Home FMCS #HC, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Hinesburg, VT: 6/26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Holyoke Water & IBEW #455, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Homer Bronson & USS, Local 5104 AAA/Hart, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Homer D. Bronson Co. and USWA, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Howard County Board of Education AAA/DC, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Hudson Phar Corp & District 1199 NY State Med Board, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Hull (Mass.) School Comm. and AFSCME Local 1395, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- IBEW 1057 & Georgia-Pacific Corporation, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- In the Matter of Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. and The Airline Pilots Associations International, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- International Paper Co & OPEIU Local 442, FMCS, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jaeger Welding Supply and Local 404 Teamsters, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- John Hancock & Insurance. Workers AAA/BOS 1of 2, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- John Hancock & Insurance. Workers AAA/BOS 2 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Jones Beloit, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Jos. T. Ryerson & Son, Inc. and USWA Local 3746, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Keebler Co. and Local 492A, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- King Philip Reg. T.A. and Reg. School District, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #1 (73-67), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #2 (73-102), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #3 (73-110), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #4 (73-115), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #5 (73-117), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #6 (73-128), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #7, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- L.I.R.R. and UTU Case #9 (73-129), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Laconia Needle & USS AAA/BOS, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Leeson Corp. and IAMAW Local 1605, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Leeson and IAM AAA, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Lindback & Teamsters, Local 379, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Lipman Marine Co. & District #15 Seafood Workers. Gloucester, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Long Island Railroad AAA(NYC), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Long Island RR & UTU AAA NYC, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Long Island RR and UTU NYC, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Ludlow Savings Bank, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Lyons Iron Works, Inc. and Shopmens Local 586, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- M.I.T. and Local 254 Bldg. Services Employees. Un., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Mack Molding & IAMAW #1199 FMCS, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Maine Central R.R. - PLB #990 Case No. 17, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #16 Case No. 16, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 1, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 10, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 11, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 12, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 14, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 15, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 18, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case NO. 19, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 2, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 20, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 21, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 22, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 3, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 4, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case NO. 6, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 7, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case No. 8, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB #990 Case NO. 9, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Maine Central R.R. PLB $990 Case No. 5, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Maine Yankee Atomic Power Co. and UWUA, Local 497 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Maine Yankee Atomic Power Co. and UWUA, Local 497 2 of 2, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Mansfield School Comm. and Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Mass. Bay Trans, Auth. and IAMAW, District 38, Local 264, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Mass. Electric Co. and U.T.W. of N.E., 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Merrow Machine & IUE #249, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Mesa. Valley Educ. Association and School District #51, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Metro Jewish Ger. & Local 144 NYSMB, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Metropolitan Mass Transit (Chicago) AAA/CHI, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Meyer Mfg. & United Steelworkers AAA/BOS, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Middlesex County Commsrs. and Local 414 AFSCME, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Milton, Vt. Jan 20, 1975 - 7:00pm (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Mississquoy Regional Valley, VT, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- MIT AAA(BOS) 1 of 2, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- MIT AAA(BOS) 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Monticello Schools AAA/NYC, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Montpelier, VT: 6/25, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Morrisville, Vt. Bd. Of School Dirs. & Morristown-Elmore T.A., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- MSAD #32 &Ashland Teachers Association AAA/BOS, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- N.J. Natural Gas Co. & IBEW, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Nashua Bd. Of Ed. and Teachers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Nashua Teachers Union and Bd. Of Ed., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- National Gypsum & USW #5476 AAA/NJ, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Naugatock Board of Educ. & Teacher AAA, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- NBC & Nabet, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- NE Telephone & IBEW AAA/BOS, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- New Bedford Gas and Edison 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- New Bedford Gas and Edison 2 of 2, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- New Britain Machine & IAM #1021, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- New Eng. Tel. Co. and Local 2317, IBEW 1 of 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- New Eng. Tel. Co. and Local 2317, IBEW 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Newport R.I. School Committee & Teachers' Association., 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Northwest &, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Northwest & ALPA 1 of 3, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Northwest & ALPA 2 of 3, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Northwest & ALPA 3 of 3, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Northwest & ALPA, S&S Div., 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Northwest Orient Airlines & ALPA, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Northwest Orient Airlines & BRAC (folder 1 of 2), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Northwest Orient Airlines & BRAC (folder 2 of 2), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Northwest Orient Airlines and ALPA 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Northwest Orient Airlines and ALPA 2 of 2, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- NY Public Library & Districted Con37 AAA/NYC, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- O'Donnell Usen Fisheries, Inc. District 15 Seafood Workers., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- OLIN Corp. and IAMAW, Local 609, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Orleans, Vt. Central Educ. Association and School Dirs. Of Lake Region, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- PA Bell Telegraph, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- PA Power & Light & Employees Independent Association AAA/Phil, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- PA Power & Light and Employees Independent Association AAA/Phil, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- PA Telephone & Telephone Workers AAA/Phil, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Pan Am 1 of 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Pan Am 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Parkwood Laminates AAABOS, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Pel Tech and Comm Coll and DSEA AAA, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Pembroke School Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Portsmouth Naval Shipyard & F.E. Metal Trades, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Portsmouth Naval Shipyard & Fed. Employees Metal Trades Council '75, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Post Newsweek & Nabet AAA/Hart, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Pratt Reed & U Furniture Workers AAA/Hart, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Process Ergr., Inc. and Boilermakers, etc., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Procter & Gamble, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Queen Anne's County: Board of Ed. & Education Association, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- R.H. Mfg. Co. and Boilermakers, etc., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- RCA and IFPTE, Local 241, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- RCA and IUE, Local 110, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Rea Express, Inc. Special Bd. Of Adjustment No. 808 1 of 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Rea Express, Inc. Special Bd. Of Adjustment No. 809 2 of 2, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Rheingold & Local 240 AAA/NYC, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Rhode Island Board of Education & Union 2012 AFT, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Rima White & IAMAW #64 AAA/Bos, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Rumford Lithographers & Brockton Printing Pressmen, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Rust Craft & Graphic Arts #67, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- S.E. Pa. Transportation Auth., 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Sad #33 Board of Directors AAA(BOS), 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Safeway Stores, Inc. and Local 400 Retail Employees. Un., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Scranton Engraving Co. and Arts Int. Un., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Scranton Times and Typo Un. Local 112, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- SE Penn Transport Authority AAA (Phil), 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Seaboard World Airlines & ALPA, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. and ALPA, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. and ALPA, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Sewing Notions, Div. of Scovill, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Silver Lake Regional School District Kingston, Mass., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Simkins & UPP, Local 457: AAA/Hart, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Simkins Industries and UPP Local 457, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Simplex & IBEW #2208 AAA/BOS, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- So. Burlington, Vt. School Bd. & Teachers, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- So. N.E. Tel. Co. and Conn. Un. Od Tel. Workers., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- South Shore Hospital & MHW, Local 880 AAA/BOS, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- ST. Alban's Vermont, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- State of N.Y. (Dept. of Mental) Hygiene & CSEA, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- State of New York & CSEA AAA/NYC, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- State of New York & CSEA AAA/NYC, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- State of New York & CSEA AAA/NYC, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Statler Tissue Industries and Local 57 United Papermakers, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Stonington Police Com & IBPO #317 AAA/Hart, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Stowe (Vt.) Board of School Dirs. Stowe Teachers' Association, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Suffolk County, N.Y. and C.S.E.A. 73-110, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sun Oil & OCAW, Local 8-901 AAA/Phil, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Sun Oil Co. and Local 8-901, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Sun Oil Co. of Pa., 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Sun Oil Co. of Pa. and Local 7-901 1 of 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Sun Oil Co. of Pa. and Local 7-901 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Sun Oil Co. of Pa. and Local 8, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Sun Oil Co. of Pa. and Local 8-901, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Thompson Steel & USS, Local 5211 AAA/Phil, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Torin Corp. and UAW Local 507, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Torrington Company and UAW Local 1645, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Tower Iron & United Steelworkers AAA/Bos, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Town of Hull School Comm. Local 1395 (Pacino), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Town of Whitman & Brotherhood of Officers AAA/Bos, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Town of Wilton, Conn. and Geo/ Peters, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Town Taxi, Inc. and Back Bay Drivers Association, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Town Taxi, Inc. and Back Bay Taxi Drivers, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Townsend Nursing Home and National Union of Hospital Employees, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Townsend, Vt. Board of School Directors, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Author AAA/NYC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Twin County Grocers and Teamsters, 863 1 of 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Twin County Grocers and Teamsters, 863 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- U of Bridgeport & AAUP AAA/Hart, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Union Carbide Corp. and Oil, Chem. & Atomic Workers, Local 8-891, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- United Postal Service & APWU, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- US Postal & (miller), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- US Postal & Amer. Postal Workers, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- US Postal & NALC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- US Postal & NALC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- US Postal & NALC O'Callaghan, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- US Postal & NALC: Caulfield, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- US Postal & Ponte, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- USPS - Letter Carriers - NB-N-1800, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- USPS & Amer. Postal Workers:, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- USPS & Letter Carriers: Battle NYC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Vergennes, VT: Addison Northwest, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Walworth Co & Braintree, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Wash. D.C. Bd. Of Ed. and Local 4, School Officers, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Wedford School Committee and Teachers' Association, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- West Haven Manor Nursing Home Local 1199, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- West Rutland, Vermont School Committee, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Westcavo Corp. and U.P.P., 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Western Mass Electric &IBEW455, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Wethersfield & IBPO #391 AAA/Hart, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Wethersfield & IBPO #391 AAA/Hart #1239, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Weyerhauser Co. and UPPI, Local 669, 1963-1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Weymouth School Comm & Teachers MTA, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Winchester, Mass. Mediation School Bd. & Teacher's Association, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Windsor Southeast District (Tierney) & Windsor Teachers Association, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- WKYC-TV & AFTRA AAA/Cleve, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Wyman Gordon AAA? BOS, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Yale & Local 35 Federation of University Employees. Gr. #2093, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Yale University and Local 35 AFL-CIO, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Yale University and Local 35, Federation Of University Employees, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Yonkers & Firefighters #628 AAA/NYC #1339, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Yonkers & Firefighters, Local 628 AAA/NYC #1339, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)